But I'm amazed you were able to come back alive after seeing that thing.
あれを見て　生きて帰って来れたとはね
To be expected of my student, I guess.
我が弟子ながら大したものだ
That's...
そんな
But rules are rules.
でも　ケジメはつけなきゃならないんだよ
You're expelled.
破門だ
Master-
師匠
Al.
アル
The trains are still running.
まだ汽車は出てる　帰りなさい
Go home.
Thanks... for everything.
お世話に　なりました
I've still got a lot of years ahead of me
この想いを　消してしまうには
Kono omoi wo keshiteshimau niwa
To just erase these feelings?
まだ人生長いでしょ？
Mada jinsei nagai desho?
To just erase these feelings?
まだ人生長いでしょ？
I want to go back and finish
やり残してるコト
Yarinokoshiteru koto
The things that I've yet to finish.
やり直してみたいから
Yarinaoshite mitai kara
I was supposed to be chasing after my ongoing dream,
夢のつづき　追いかけていたはずなのに
Yume no tsuzuki oikaketeita hazu nanoni
Yet I faltered over others while walking this thin, winding path.
曲がりくねった　細い道　人につまずく
Magarikunetta hosoi michi hito ni tsumazuku
It's not that I want to return to those days.
あの頃みたいにって　戻りたい訳じゃないの
Ano koro mitainitte modoritai wake ja nai no
I'm searching for the sky I lost.
無くしてきた空を　探してる
Nakushitekita sora wo sagashiteru
Don't make that sad face, as if you've fallen victim.
わかってくれますように
Wakatte kuremasu youni
As if you want people to pity you.
犠牲になったような　悲しい顔はやめてよ
Gisei ni natta youna kanashii kao wa yameteyo
Tears aren't the end of your sins.
罪の最後は涙じゃないよ
Tsumi no saigo wa namida ja nai yo
You have to bear them painfully, forever.
ずっと苦しく背負ってくんだ
Zutto kurushiku seottekunda
Who are you waiting for in the maze of emotions,
出口見えない感情迷路に
Deguchi mienai kanjoumeiro ni
Where you can't even see the exit?
誰を待ってるの？
Dare wo matteruno?
I want to blurt it out more justly,
白いノートに綴ったように
Shiroi nooto ni tsuzutta youni
Just like how I wrote it in my white notebook.
もっと素直に吐き出したいよ
Motto sunao ni hakidashitai yo
What do you want to run from?
何から　逃れたいんだ
Nani kara nogaretainda
That thing called "reality"?
…現実ってやつ？
Genjitsu tte yatsu?
I just want to scream out,
叶えるために　生きてるんだって
Kanaeru tame ni ikiterundatte
"I'm only living to fulfill my wish." Can you hear me?
叫びたくなるよ　聞こえていますか？
Sakebitaku naru yo kikoeteimasuka?
I can't take the safe way out of everything.
無難になんて　やってられないから
Bunan ni nante yatterarenaikara
I don't even have a place to return to.
…帰る場所も無いの
Kaeru basho mo nai no
I'm always thankful for everyone's kindness,
優しさには　いつも感謝してる
Yasashisa ni wa itsumo kansha shiteru
That's why I want to become stronger. (I'm on the way)
だから強くなりたい(I'm on the the
(I'm on the way)
Dakara tsuyoku naritai (I'm on the way)
This is reminding me of the old days.
懐かしくなる
Natsukashiku naru
This pain is all right with me.
こんな痛みも歓迎じゃん
Konna itami mo kangei jan
Drop by if you're ever in the neighborhood.
また近くに来たら寄れよ
But we're...
でも　僕たち
Idiot!
バカ野郎
If you aren't in a master-student relationship anymore,
師匠でも弟子でもなくなったってことは
it means that from now on,
you're going to treat each other as individuals.
これからは一人の人間として
対等に接するってことだ
What's holding you back?
何を遠慮することがある
くそっ
Dammit!
Al! What did we come to Dublith for?
アル　オレたち何しにダブリスまで来たんだ
Mr. Sig, we're going to head back!
シグさん　オレたち先に戻ります
Don't let her kill you.
殺されるなよ
Master!
師匠
What did you come back for?!
どの面下げて戻ってきた
Who are you calling Master?!
何が師匠だ
You guys aren't my students anymore!
貴様らなんぞ弟子とは思わん　とっとと帰れ
Go home already!
Master!
師匠
We came here to find clues on how to get our bodies back.
僕たち　元の体に戻る手がかりを得にここに来たんです
We can't go back with nothing.
手ぶらでは帰れません
帰れ
Go home!
We won't!
嫌です
バカタレが
Morons...
You didn't see the truth, did you, Al?
アルは真理を見なかったんだね
No. I have no idea what you mean...
はい　なんのことかさっぱり
Maybe you lost your memories due to shock.
ショックで記憶が飛んでいるのかもしれないね
How about we try retrieving your memories?
記憶を戻してみようか
You had your whole body taken.
全身を持ってかれてるんだ
There's no way you didn't see it.
あれを見ていないはずがない
I get it!
そうか　オレや師匠は体の一部分だけど
You and I only had parts of our bodies taken, so if it's based on how much we paid, Al should know the most of the truth!
支払った通行料の多さでいうなら
アルが一番真理に詳しいはずだ
じゃあ　そのときの記憶が戻れば
So if we can get my memories back, we might find a clue on how to get our bodies back...
体を取り戻す手がかりが
But memories of that thing, huh?
しかしあれの記憶か
That thing, huh?
あれねぇ
Huh? Could this be bad?
なんかやばい
More like... extraordinary?
やばいっていうかすごい
Yeah, you could call it that.
うん　なんかすごい
Your mind might explode...
精神がいかれるかも
If you screw up, it could destroy you...
ヘタすりゃ　廃人
But if it'll let us find a clue...
それでも　手がかりがつかめるなら
I want to do it!
それにすがりたい
Fine.
分かった　記憶を戻す方法を
Let me ask a friend of mine how to regain one's memories.
私の知人に聞いてみよう
But before that, let's eat.
だが　その前にご飯だ
You'd better help out.
手伝いな
Yes, ma'am!
はい
No doubt about it. That's the guy who affixed a soul.
間違いねぇ　あいつが魂を錬成したヤツだ
East City
Eastern Headquarters
You'll be working in Central starting next week.
君　来週から中央勤務ね
Yes, sir.
はい
It'll become quiet around here.
ここも寂しくなるね
You were quite the flashy one.
君　いろいろと派手だったから
Not anywhere near as flashy as you were in your prime, sir.
いえいえ
将軍の若いころほどでは
I was able to relax because you worked so hard.
君が一生懸命やってくれたお陰で　わしも楽ができたよ
But I also learned a lot from all of those jobs you gave me.
私もさまざまな仕事を任せていただいたお陰で
見識が広がりました
Check.
チェック
I was finally able to beat you.
最後にやっと勝てました
Let's call this victory a parting gift.
この１勝は　餞別だな
General.
将軍
I'd also like to ask for another gift.
餞別ついでに　ちょうだいしたいものが
Sgt. Major Kain Fuery.
ケイン·フュリー曹長
Warrant Officer Vato Falman.
ヴァトー·ファルマン准尉
2nd Lt. Heymans Breda.
ハイマンス·ブレダ少尉
2nd Lt. Jean Havoc.
ジャン·ハボック少尉
Lieutenant Riza Hawkeye.
リザ·ホークアイ中尉
The five of you will be transferring to Central with me.
以上５名　私とともにセントラルへ異動となった
I won't take any complaints.
文句は言わせん　ついてこい
Come with me!
Colonel, I can't.
大佐　まずいっす
I just recently found a girlfriend.
オレ最近　彼女できたばっかなんすよ
Break up with her.
別れろ
Again?!
またかよ
Your wounds haven't even healed yet.
まだ傷口もふさがってないってのに
Master...
師父
I'm so happy to see you're well.
ご無事で何より
I heard rumors about you going around killing State Alchemists.
国家錬金術師を殺してまわっているそうだな
I understand your resentment.
恨みたい気持ちは分かる
The ones who annihilated our village were State Alchemists.
確かに　我らの村を焼き滅ぼしたのは国家錬金術師だ
But all revenge does is give birth to more revenge.
しかし復讐は　新たな復讐の芽を育てるだけだ
そんな不毛な連鎖は　早々に断ち切らねばならん
A futile chain like that must be stopped immediately.
You must persevere.
堪えねばならんのだよ
Sorry to interrupt.
じゃまするぜ
おお　本当にいた
Whoa, he really was here!
An Ishbalan with a cross scar on his forehead.
バッテン傷のイシュヴァール人
We're splitting the prize money like we agreed, Mr. Yoki.
約束どおり　賞金は山分けだぜ　ヨキさん
Huh? Where's Mr. Yoki?
あれ　ヨキさんがいねぇなぁ
Hey!
あんた
どういうつもりなんだい
What's this all about?
You had nowhere to go, so we treated you like family-
行く当てのないあんたを　ここのみんなは家族のように
うるさい
Shut up!
Don't go comparing me with you Ishbalans!
お前たちイシュヴァール人と一緒にするな
I'm going to rise again!
私は再びのし上がるのだ
I'm going to keep rising and rising,
and eventually get rid of that damned Edward Elric!
のし上がって のし上がって
にっくき　エドワード·エルリックを追い落とすのだ
Now you two, please do your thing.
さあ　おふた方　やっちゃってください
Seems I'll only bring trouble while I'm here.
オレがここにいては迷惑になるようだ
You're an obedient one.
聞き分けのいいヤツだ
Y-You bastard! What did you do?!
てっ　てめぇ　何しやがった
I'll give you some time to pray to God.
神に祈る間をやろう
G-God? You seriously think I believe-
なっ　何が神だ　んなもん
待って　来ないで
Wait!
Stay away!
わ　私が悪ぅございました
I-I was wrong!
Please spare my life!
命ばかりはお助けを　一生ついていきますから
I'll follow you forever!
Are you going?
行くのか
兄が悲しむぞ
You'll sadden your brother.
There's no going back for me.
もう　後戻りはできぬのです
Here he comes.
来たぞ
We were waiting for you, guest.
待ってたぜ　客人
"We know your secret."
「お前の秘密を知っている　デビルズネストへ来い」
"Come to Devil's Nest."
Are you the ones who know this "secret"?
おじさんたちが秘密を知ってる人
We sure are. We know quite a lot.
おお　知ってるぜ　いろいろとな
I also want to know my own secret.
僕も　僕の秘密を知りたいと思っている
Then it's settled.
なら話は簡単だ　オレについてこい
Follow me.
But my master taught me not to follow strangers.
でも知らない人についていっちゃいけないって
師匠に習ったよ
How old are you?
おめぇはいくつよ
Fourteen.
If you're fourteen, shouldn't you be able to make your own decisions?
１４ったら　もう一人で考えて行動できる年だろ
You can't be saying things like "master taught me" forever.
「師匠が」とかいつまでも言ってちゃダメだぞ
I see! I have to make my own decisions then, huh?
そうか　自分で考えなきゃね
That's right!
そうとも　だからオレたちと 一緒に
So come with-
So I decided to tie you guys up and beat the secrets out of you.
自分で考えた結果
おじさんたちをふん縛って
秘密とやらを聞くことにしたよ
So in the end, you chose force.
結局は力ずくか
I'm coming in!
おじゃまするわよ
Y-You're inside-
なっ 中に
Hey, stay put!
ちょっと　おとなしくしなさい
どう　中から体を動かされる気分は
How does it feel to have your body controlled from the inside?
Even if you do this, you can't stop my movements completely!
こんなことしたって
僕の動きを完全に止めることなんてできない
You're right. But...
そうね　でも
As long as I can restrict your movements just a bit...
少し動きを鈍らせれば
We can win the fight.
カタがつく
Did I hurt you?
ケガはないか
I hit my head.
頭打ったわ
Giving us trouble...
手間掛けさせやがって
Who are you guys...
おじさんたちは一体
They're chimeras.
そいつらは合成獣
My henchmen.
オレの手下だ
Wow, that's so cool! You really are empty.
おお　すげぇ
本当に空っぽだぜ
I'm Greed.
オレはグリード
Let's try to get along.
まっ　仲よくやろうや
おにいさんたち本当は何者なの
What are you guys, really?
合成獣なんてウソでしょ
You were lying about being chimeras, right?
There's no way chimeras can talk!
だって　合成獣が言葉を話すはずがない
There's no way "there's no way".
ありえない　なんてことはありえない
Since this girl who's inside you right now is a chimera that was transmuted with a snake.
現にお前の中にいるこのねえちゃんは
蛇と合成された合成獣だ
And Loa, who's behind me... What are you again?
オレの後ろにいる
ロア　お前なんだっけ
A cow?
牛
Yes.
ええ
Other than that, we've got a lizard and a crocodile.
ほかにもトカゲにワニ
The guy you fought earlier takes a piss with one leg up.
さっき坊主が手合わせしたヤツなんざ
片足上げて小便するぜ
I do not!
しませんよ
犬なの
You're a dog?
Yeah. It's pretty useful.
ああ　なかなか便利だぜ
No way...
ありえない　やっぱりありえないよ
That can't be true!
第一誰が合成に成功したっていうのさ
And besides, who are you going to say performed the transmutation successfully?
The army.
軍だよ
そんな
No way...
とにかくだ
Anyway, it just means there's a flip side to this world that society doesn't know about.
世の中には日の当たらない裏の世界があるってこった
On a different note, I'm not a chimera.
ちなみにオレは合成獣じゃねぇ
I'm a homunculus.
人造人間だ
Homunculus?!
人造人間
You've heard of them, haven't you?
知ってるだろう　人工的につくられた人間
Humans that were created artificially.
That's what I am.
それがオレだ
Homunculus?
人造人間
It's another name for an android.
人造人間のことさ
But it's said in the book that you're not allowed to create humans.
人間はつくっちゃいけないって本に書いてあったよ
You're lying!
ウソだ
I've never even heard of anyone creating a homunculus!
人造人間が成功したなんて話聞いたことがない
Geez...
やれやれ
Let me show you some proof.
証拠を見せてやる
W-What did you do that for?!
なっ　なんてことするんだ
これで１回死亡だ
That's one death for me.
No way...
そんな
Do you understand now?
分かったか
ありえないなんてことはありえない
There's no way "there's no way".
Besides, aren't you living proof of that?
何よりお前の存在がそれを証明してるだろ
An existence with a soul and no body.
魂だけの存在のお前がよ
どうしてそれを
How did you...
I know just about everything that goes on in this other world.
オレの耳には　裏の世界のことは大抵入ってくる
Let's get to the point.
さて　本題に入ろう
魂のみで死ぬことのない体ってのは
How does it feel to be immortal with just a soul?
どんな気分だ
Transmuting a soul and affixing it to another object.
個人の魂だけを錬成し　ほかの物に定着させる
If you do it correctly, that person can gain eternal life.
やりようによっては永遠の生命を手に入れられる
Am I wrong?
違うか
オレはグリード　強欲だからよ
I'm Greed.
I'm greedy,
so I want money, women, status, fame, and everything else in this world!
金も欲しい　女も欲しい
地位も名誉も
この世のすべてが欲しい
そして　永遠の生命もだ
And I want eternal life!
But aren't you already immortal?
だって不死身なんじゃ
I was made pretty durable,
ちょいと丈夫につくられちまったんでな
２００年近く生きてはいる
so I've been alive for almost two hundred years.
But I'm not quite immortal.
だが不死身ってわけでもねぇんだ
Now, I've told you my secret.
さぁて　オレの秘密は教えたぜ
It's your turn.
次はお前の番だ
教えてくれ　その体の秘密を
Tell me the secret to that body.
You should spill it.
しゃべった方がいいわよ
You don't want to be taken apart and dissected, do you?
バラバラに解体されて　調べられたくはないでしょ
It's impossible.
無理だよ
I don't have any memories of when I became like this,
僕にはこの体になったときの記憶がないし
and I'm not the one who performed the transmutation.
錬成したのは僕じゃない
I don't know anything.
僕は何も知らないんだ
Then what about the guy who did it?
じゃあ　その錬成してくれたヤツだ
そいつに聞けばいい
We can ask him.
That's...
それは
Where the heck did Al disappear to?
アルのヤツ　どこ行っちまったんだ
I don't mind telling ya.
教えてやってもいいですぜ
If you tell us his secret, that is.
弟さんの秘密を教えてくれたら
Brother!
兄さん
I would never have expected you to get kidnapped.
まさかお前が誘拐されるとはな
Brother, this guy's a homunculus!
兄さん　この人人造人間だ
Homunculus?
人造人間
Hey, don't go blowing my secret!
お前　いきなりバラすなよ
だから
So he might have a hint on how to get our bodies back!
僕たちが元の体に戻るヒントを持ってるかもしれない
ウロボロスの入れ墨
Tattoo of Ouroboros.
That's how it is.
そういうわけ
It would have been easier if we could have just settled things with the armor boy.
鎧君だけで事が済めば楽だったんだけどよ
連中と仲間だってんなら直接聞けよ
If you're buddies with them,
why don't you just ask them yourself?
"Them"?
連中
その入れ墨をした連中が第五研究所にいた
There were people with that tattoo at Research Laboratory 5.
And there, I met a guy who had
his soul affixed to a piece of armor.
そこで鎧に魂を定着したヤツと会った
Seriously?
そうなの
Well, for certain reasons,
まっ　ちと訳ありでな
I can't really do that.
そういうわけにもいかないんだ
So let's discuss this.
そこで物は相談だ
You two want to get your bodies back, right?
お前ら二人は肉体を取り戻したい　そうだな
I'll teach you how to create a homunculus.
オレはお前に　人造人間の製造方法を教える
そのかわり　お前はオレに魂の錬成方法を教えろ
And in exchange, you teach me how to transmute a soul.
It's called equivalent exchange.
等価交換ってやつさ
But seriously...
とはいえ
やっぱ元の肉体取り戻す必要あんのか
Is there even a need to get your body back?
Personally, I think that body can be somewhat useful.
その体　便利でいいと思うぜ
いくない
No, it's not!
You think so?
そうかぁ
You don't get hungry,
you don't get sleepy, you don't get tired.
腹も減らねぇ　眠くもならねぇ　疲れねぇって
Sounds awesome to me!
最高じゃねぇ
Cut... The...
ふざけたことを
ぬかしてんじゃねぇ
...Shit!!!
便利だ　最高だ
Useful?! Awesome?!
You don't know anything,
and yet you're spewing all this bullshit?!
何も知らねぇヤツが黙って聞いてりゃ
勝手なことぬかしやがって
How to transmute a soul?!
魂の錬成方法だ
んなもんミジンコ１匹分もくれてやるいわれはねぇ
You're not getting an ounce of it from me!!!
If you're a villain, I'll beat you up, smack you,
punch the information out of you and snatch it!!
悪党は
ボコる　どつく　吐かせる　もぎ取る
In other words, I get all and you get nothing!
すなわちオレの総取り
悪党とは等価交換の必要なぁしぃ
There's no need for equivalent exchange when dealing with a villain!!!
Guess we have to use force again.
結局　また力ずくかよ
Don't kill him.
殺すなよ
Fine, fine.
へいへい
どっかの死刑囚より遅ぇ
I met a guy on death row who was a lot faster than you!
次
Next.
Loa, take the armor boy with you.
ロア　鎧君連れてけ
We'll take him apart and dissect him.
バラして解析する
はっ
Roger.
ちょっ ちょっと
H-Hey!
Wait!
待て
Useless.
無駄無駄
With a steel sword like that, you can't even add a scratch to this ultimate shield!
その鋼の剣じゃ　この最強の盾は傷一つ付けられねぇよ
Your head's wide open!
脳天がら空き
Oww... that hurt.
おお 痛ぇ
If I was an ordinary human,
I'd need to go to the hospital for this.
普通の人間だったら病院送りだぞ
Yeah, but you're not really ordinary at all.
全然普通じゃねぇのな
Well, my body is normal,
いや体は普通なんだけど
but I've got a little bit of regeneration, and I have the ultimate shield.
ちょいと再生能力が過ぎるのと
最強の盾があるだけだ
分かったろ　お前はオレに勝てねぇ
Get it now?
You can't beat me.
It'd be smarter to just make the trade.
取り引きした方が利口だぜ
Oh, you're one of those people, aren't you?
お前　あれだな
You don't care if you get covered in wounds,
自分が傷だらけになるのは平気だが
but if your relatives get hurt,
you can't take it and lose your cool.
身内がちょっとでも傷つくのは
耐えられなくて冷静さを失う
How foolish.
愚かだな
You're going to let your strong feelings take over like that and lose important information and your brother?
そうやって激情に任せて
貴重な情報も弟も失うか
I'll go get my brother back after I beat your ass.
てめぇを倒したら弟も取り戻しに行くさ
Your regeneration ability isn't endless, right?
無限の再生能力じゃないんだろ
As long as I keep hitting the part of you that's flesh, then...
生身の部分をボコり続けりゃ
My bad, sorry for going easy on you.
こりゃ悪かったなぁ　手抜きしちまって
This turns me into an ugly guy,
so I don't really like to show people.
ちょっとブ男になるんで　あんまり見せたくねぇんだよ
Didn't I say so?
言っただろ
You won't even be able to scratch me.
お前はオレに傷一つ付けることができねぇ
I found this in the back alley of West Street.
西通りの路地裏に落ちてた
Al disappeared... and now Ed, too.
アルが消えて　エドまでも
Those idiots! I may even have to make them students again and teach them about taking care of personal belongings!
あのバカども
もっぺん弟子入りさせて
物を大切にしろってとこからたたき直してやるか
I've got it!
分かりましたよ
I heard someone who looks like Ed went into a bar called Devil's Nest.
さっき　エド君らしき男の子が
デビルズネストって酒場に入ってったそうですよ
You dead?
死んだか
Good! Kids should be lively.
よし　いいぞ　子供は元気でなくちゃな
No matter how many times you try, you can't win.
何度やってもお前は勝てねぇ
さぁて　秘密を吐いてもらおうか
How about you tell me the secret now?
Thanks for that.
ありがとよ
The blood that was all up in my head went away, and I can think clearly now.
頭に上ってた血が少し抜けて
脳みそがさえてきた
That's my mechanic for ya.
さすがうちの整備士だ
It still moves after all this.
こんなんなってもまだ動く
って　まだ抵抗するかよ
You're still going to resist?
Let this put you to sleep!
これでもうおとなしく寝てろ
I'm solid, aren't I?
オレ　硬ぇよな
That's weird...
おかしいな
So what?!
これがどうした
What, don't you have anything else?!
ワンパターンだな　こんなもん
What the hell... did you do to my shield....
オレの盾に何をしやがった
It's simple if you think about it.
考えてみりゃ簡単なことだ
You said you're a homunculus, but if your body is normal, that means a third of your body is made up of carbon.
人造人間つっても体が普通なら
構成物質の３分の１は炭素でできてるってことだ
Depending on how the carbon atoms are combined, the toughness can range from a pencil tip's to a diamond's.
炭素原子は結合の度合いによって
鉛筆の芯からダイヤモンドにまで硬さを変える
If you know that much, then it's all a matter of alchemy.
そこまで分かりゃ　あとは錬金術の分野だ
Good!
いいぞ　こうでなくちゃおもしろくねぇ
Otherwise, it wouldn't be fun!
And now, I just figured something out!
そして今分かったことが一つ
You can't harden and regenerate at the same time!
硬化と再生を一度にすることはできない
My first impression of you was that of a reckless idiot.
ただの猪突猛進なバカガキかと思ったが
But how many more times can you attack me with that body?
だが　その体であと何回攻撃できる
はい　ちょっと失礼するよ
Hi, coming in.
M-Master!
せ　師匠
You dumbass!!!
こんのバカタレがぁ
You don't even care enough to put away a single broomstick?!
ほうき一つ片づけもせんと何やっとるんだ
I-I'm sorry!
す　すみません
私の身内の者が　随分と世話になったようだね
Looks like you gave my boys quite a bit of trouble.
師匠　こいつ
Master! He's...
I know.
分かってるよ
I could hear you all the way from the hallway.
廊下まであんたの声は筒抜けだった
Come on, give me a break.
おいおい　勘弁してくれよ
I don't really like fighting women-
オレは女と戦う趣味は
What... the hell are you?!
てめぇ　一体何者だ
A passing...
通りすがりの
主婦だぁ
...housewife!!!
Say, the sky we saw that day, the scarlet sky.
あの日見た空　茜色の空を
Ano hi mita sora akaneiro no sora wo
Do you remember it from that day?
ねえ　君は覚えていますか
Nee kimi wa oboeteimasuka
We made a promise and a vow while the early summer wind circled us.
約束　契り　初夏の風が包む
Yakusoku chigiri shoka no kaze ga tsutsumu
And we clung close together.
二人　寄り添った
Futari yorisotta
Your forced smile
無理な笑顔の裏
Muri na egao no ura
Holds elongated shadows.
伸びた影をかくまう
Nobita kage wo kakumau
I pretend not to notice and continue on.
だから　気づかぬふり　再生を選ぶ
Dakara kizukanu furi saisei wo erabu
All the while waiting for you to deliver some news at the table.
テーブルの上の　震えない知らせ　待ち続けて
Teeburu no ue no furuenai shirase machitsuzukete
Empty nights, mornings that will never arrive,
空白の夜も　来るはずのない朝も
Kuuhaku no yoru mo kuru hazu no nai asa mo
I could see them from a mile away.
全部わかってたんだ
Zenbu wakattetanda
Say, the sky we saw that day, the scarlet sky.
あの日見た空　茜色の空を
Ano hi mita sora akaneiro no sora wo
I'm sure you'll remember it one day.
ねえ　 いつか思い出すでしょう
Nee itsuka omoidasu deshou
While holding the promise we couldn't keep,
果たせなかった　約束を抱いて
Hatasenakatta yakusoku wo idaite
We take our first steps down our own paths.
二人　歩き出す
Futari arukidasu
日本語字幕仕上げ：FAYFAY
Those who are strong are destined to yield to ones who are far stronger.
強き者は
更に強大な力によって　屈伏される運命にある
漫遊字幕組
http://popgo.net/bbs
But their souls will not lose as long as they have pride.
だが　魂は負けない
そこに矜持があるかぎり
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
次回　鋼の錬金術師
FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST
Episode 14, Those Who Lurk Underground.
第十四話　地下にひそむ者たち
見えているものだけが　すべてではない
There's more than meets the eye.
賢者の石を何に使う
手に入れる　不老不死の法を
東の大国　シンからの来訪者
この国にも　錬丹術関連で調べに来た
錬丹術
アメストリスに潜む大いなる闇
俺はリンヨウ　よろしく
賢者の石と不老不死の法をめぐる陰謀
それじゃそろそろその面を拝ませてもらおうか
鋼の錬金術師　FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST
七月十二日より　新章突入